I don't know if it has ever happened to you that
you were walking down the street
calmly and suddenly you do
eye contact with another person
and it's something very special
I don't know how to describe it, there's something there.
as a connection between two strangers who
they don't know each other
I don't know if this has happened to you
time but the time I remember most was
when one day I was walking in Madrid
along Gran Vía in the center with my friends
and the Gran Via street was full, full
full of people but above all
heads there was a boy who was taller
then he looked out above all
heads and made eye contact
and it was an immediate connection I smiled
he smiled
and we each continue on our own path
It was that one second two seconds but
I still remember, I remember too
who had short blond hair more or less
and a short-sleeved t-shirt but I don't
I remember his face very well.
The truth is that at that moment if the
street would not have been so crowded and not
there would have been so many people maybe
I would have gone and talked to him
I regret I regret not having gone
to talk to him because who knows what
better now we would have a relationship
super close but I didn't do it when
I want to say something to a stranger in the
street to a person I don't know and who
I will never see them again in my life.
I'm going to insult them or I'm going to say something
I want to tell you bad because I like you
t-shirt
If I want to tell you that I like your
If the shirt doesn't fit, I'll become super.
shy for some reason I don't know why
I get super shy and more time passes
suffering in thinking
I tell him or I don't tell him I tell him or
I don't tell him
if not if he didn't spend more time thinking about
this
telling him if he thought about it once and
I said I like your shirt and I said it
I would suffer less but for some reason I
I come back super shy super shy and it gives me
I'm ashamed I don't want to say it even if it is
something good that the other person will like
person, I don't know if that happens to you
also
leave it in a comment because
I'm better off alone, I don't believe, I don't believe that
be just me
However, when I meet a person
new that is likely to see more
times
In this case I am super launched I am super
open and nice to meet you
Well, actually I don't say that like that.
My name is Laura, how are you? I don't know what and if I
You like me and there is a connection, I can help you.
tell my dreams and hopes to the
ten minutes of knowing you or so
easy indeed if you see me from the outside
Anyone would say that I am a person
super extroverted but actually
according to the millions of tests that are in
internet
I am an introverted person
I am introverted at first no
understood how a person like me
that are launched and so open to
meet new people
may be introverted I didn't understand no
I understood how my could fit in
personality when meeting people with being
introverted
It is true that I enjoy time a lot
when I'm alone but still like that
Being an introvert didn't suit me.
I mean yes but not until one day
I took it and searched on the internet, it's normal
feeling exhausted after being with
people didn't come to me so often
being tired after seeing a
friend who for a moment I thought I don't know
The best thing is a disease or something that
I have, I don't know, but it was then when
I read in a forum
It is completely normal because
seen that is what it means to be
introvert an introverted person is
a person who recharges when he is alone
your batteries take energy and strength rest
and when he's with people he lets go of all that
energy and an extroverted person is
just the opposite when you are with
people you recharge and get energy and without
However, when you are extroverted and spend
time alone all that energy you have
collected while being with people, the loose ones
which is a rather strange concept
for me it doesn't quite fit in
the head
you who are extroverted or
introverts anyway this is what I
has been going through the lately
head and by the way today I'm recording
with my cell phone because it's broken
microphone once again so I'm
waiting for the microphone to reach me
new to be able to make videos with a
good audio
have a nice day
chao